A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Washington, DC, Series O FA350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs (SAP), December 1954-December 1955; 7; 14.4 Cubic Feet
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Appointments and Resignation (Box 61, Folder 510)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 1.
  - Charter and Reports - NAR - Progress, Status and Action Reports (Box 61, Folder 511)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 2.
  - Over-all Report to the President (Box 61, Folder 512)
  - Over-all Report to the President (drafts, etc.) (Box 61, Folder 513)
  - Planning Coordination Group - Agendas and Minutes, Members and Alternates (Box 61, Folder 514)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 3.
  - Planning Coordination Group - Establishment, Functions, and History (Box 61, Folder 515)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 4.
  - Planning Coordination Group - Position Room (Box 62, Folder 516)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 5.
  - Cold War Organization - Rockefeller Plan, December 1955 (Box 62, Folder 517)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 6.
  - Cold War Organization - Operations Coordinating Board Establishment (Box 62, Folder 518)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 7.
  - Cold War Organization - Establishment of Planning Coordination Group (Box 62, Folder 519)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 8.
  - Cold War Organization - Operations Coordinating Board Effectiveness, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 520)
  - Cold War Organization - Sarnoff Plan and American Legion Plan (Box 62, Folder 521)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 9.
  - Cold War Organization - Jackson Report, June 30, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 522)
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) (Office for Free World Cooperation) - Final Report, February 18, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 523)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 10.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Assignments and Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 524)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 11.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Operations Alert (Box 63, Folder 525)
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Drafts of Final Report (Box 63, Folder 526)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 12.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Psychological Warfare - Drafts (Box 63, Folder 527)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 13.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Economic Warfare - Drafts and Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 528)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 14.
  - Quantico I - Vulnerabilities Panel, June 5-10, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 529)
  - Quantico I - Vulnerabilities Panel, June 5-10, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 530)
  - Quantico I - Vulnerabilities Panel, June 5-10, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 531)
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-conference (Box 64, Folder 532)
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-conference (Box 64, Folder 533)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 15.
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-conference (Box 65, Folder 534)
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-conference (Box 65, Folder 535)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 16.
  - Four-Power Conference - Presidential Statements and Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 536)
  - Four-Power Conference - Conference - Verbatim Records (Box 66, Folder 537)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 17.
  - Four-Power Conference - Disarmament (Box 66, Folder 538)
  - Four-Power Conference - Post-Geneva (Box 66, Folder 539)
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, Verbatim Records, July 19-22, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 540)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 18.
  - Four-Power Conference - Aerial Inspection - Overflight (Box 66, Folder 541)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 19.
  - Four-Power Conference - Aerial Inspection - Overflight (Exhibit) (Box 66, Folder 542)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 20.
  - Four-Power Conference - Aerial Inspection - Overflight (News Clips) (Box 67, Folder 543)
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, State Department Position Papers, October 1955 (Box 67, Folder 544)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 21.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, October 1955 (Box 67, Folder 545)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 22.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, East-West Contacts, October 1955 (Box 67, Folder 546)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 23.
  - Quantico II - Establishment, Membership, Meetings, and Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 547)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 24.
  - Quantico II - Final Report, "Psychological Aspects of Future United States Strategy" (Box 68, Folder 548)
  - Quantico II - Background Papers (Box 68, Folder 549)
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Source Papers 1 through 7 (Box 69, Folder 550)
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Source Papers 8 through 15 (Box 69, Folder 551)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 25.
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Source Papers 16 through 21 (Box 69, Folder 552)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 26.
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Final Report (Box 70, Folder 553)
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Final Report (Box 70, Folder 554)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 27.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerablilities - Progress Report and Outline Plan (Box 70, Folder 555)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 29.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerablilities - Background Papers (Box 70, Folder 556)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 28.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerablilities - Development of Vulnerabilities Paper (Box 70, Folder 557)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 1, Folder 30.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerablilities - Policy Papers (Box 71, Folder 558)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 32.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerablilities - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 559)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 33.
  - Escapees and Refugees (Defection and Redefection) (Box 71, Folder 560)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 34.
  - Escapees and Refugees (Defection and Redefection) (Box 71, Folder 561)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 35.
  - NSC - Scientific Satellite Program (Box 71, Folder 562)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 36.
  - NSC - Basic Policy Papers (Box 71, Folder 563)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 37.
  - NSC - Volunteer Freedom Corps (Box 71, Folder 564)
  - NSC - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 71, Folder 565)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 38.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Overseas Education Program (Box 72, Folder 566)
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, December 1954-June 1955 (Box 72, Folder 567)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 39, Folder 39.1, and Folder 39.2.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Minutes of Meetings (Box 72, Folder 568)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 31.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Working Groups (Box 73, Folder 569)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 41.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, July 1955-January 1956 (Box 73, Folder 570)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 40, Folder 40.1, and Folder 40.2.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 571)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 42.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - NSC and OCB Papers (Box 73, Folder 572)
    National Security Council and Operations Coordinating Board
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 43.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Bilateral Agreements (Box 73, Folder 573)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 44.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Background and Development of 50-50 Program (Box 73, Folder 574)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 45.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Atomic Ship (Box 73, Folder 575)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 46.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - President's Penn State Speech (Box 74, Folder 576)
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Power Reactors (Box 74, Folder 577)
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Soviet Activities and Geneva Conference (Box 74, Folder 578)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 47.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Reactor Paper (Box 74, Folder 579)
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Procedures (Message to Congress) (Box 75, Folder 580)
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - General (Box 75, Folder 581)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 48.
  - Cabinet Meetings (Box 75, Folder 582)
  - Churchill Medal (Box 75, Folder 583)
  - President's Gettysburg Farm (Box 75, Folder 584)
  - Imprisoned Fliers (Box 75, Folder 585)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 49.
  - International Research Institute, Princeton, New Jersey (Free and Cantril) (Box 76, Folder 586)
  - Miscellaneous Projects (Box 76, Folder 587)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 50.
  - Organization, Personnel, and Security (Box 76, Folder 588)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 51.
  - Moral Rearmament (Box 76, Folder 589)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 52.
  - Press Relationships, White House (Box 76, Folder 590)
  - Procedures, Equipment, and Supplies (Box 76, Folder 591)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 53.
  - Richardson Foundation (Box 77, Folder 592)
  - Tables and Chairs - to President (Box 77, Folder 593)
  - United Nations (Box 77, Folder 594)
  - Foreign Economic Policy - General (Box 77, Folder 595)
  - Foreign Economic Policy - Trade Policy, GATT, and CEEP (Box 77, Folder 596)
  - Foreign Economic Policy - Soviet Activities (Box 77, Folder 597)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 2, Folder 54.
  - Foreign Economic Policy - Asia (Box 78, Folder 598)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 55.
  - Militant Liberty (Action), Book I (Box 78, Folder 599)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 56.
  - Militant Liberty (Action), Book II (Box 78, Folder 600)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 57.
  - Militant Liberty (Action), Book III (Box 78, Folder 601)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 58.
  - Dynamic Democracy, April 28, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 602)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 59.
  - Public Opinion Reports (Box 78, Folder 603)
  - Public Opinion Reports - General (Box 79, Folder 604)
  - Public Opinion - Factors Relating to Four-Power Conference, June 11, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 605)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 60.
  - Public Opinion - Western European and American Opinion Relating to the Four-Power Conference, July 9, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 606)
  - Public Opinion - Western Europe after Four-Power Conference, August 3, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 607)
  - Public Opinion - Trends in the Aftermath of Geneva, September 23, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 608)
  - Public Opinion - Additional Factors in Western European Opinion About Foreign Ministers Conference, October 15, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 609)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 61.
  - Public Opinion - American Public Opinion on International Issues, October 1955 (Box 79, Folder 610)
  - Public Opinion - Trends After Foreign Ministers Conference, December 30, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 611)
  - Public Opinion - Daily Opinion Summaries, Department of State (Box 80, Folder 612)
  - Public Opinion - American Opinion (Special Reports), Department of State (Box 80, Folder 613)
  - Public Opinion - American Opinion (Series Reports), Department of State (Box 80, Folder 614)
  - Cultural Activities - Cinerama; Porgy and Bess; and Soviet Union (Box 80, Folder 615)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 62.
  - Cultural Activities - Proposed Study Group; Exchange of Persons (Box 80, Folder 616)
  - Cultural Activities - President's Emergency Fund (Box 80, Folder 617)
  - Cultural Activities - President's Emergency Fund (Box 80, Folder 618)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 63.
  - Cultural Activities - Books Overseas (Box 81, Folder 619)
  - Cultural Activities - General (Box 81, Folder 620)
  - Salk Polio Vaccine - General (Box 81, Folder 621)
  - Salk Polio Vaccine - Official Statements (Box 81, Folder 622)
  - Salk Polio Vaccine - International Distribution (Box 81, Folder 623)
  - President - United Nations Speech (Box 82, Folder 624)
  - President - NAR Corespondence (Box 82, Folder 625)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 64.
  - President's Press Conferences (Box 82, Folder 626)
  - President's Speeches (Box 82, Folder 627)
  - Secretary of State - NAR Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 628)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 65.
  - Secretary of State - Speeches and Statements (Box 82, Folder 629)
  - State Department - General (Box 82, Folder 630)
  - United States Information Agency - Policy Papers (Box 82, Folder 631)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 66.
  - United States Information Agency - Publications and Soviet Propaganda Activities (Box 83, Folder 632)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 67.
  - United States Information Agency - General (Box 83, Folder 633)
  - Departments and Agencies - General (Box 83, Folder 634)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 68.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism - Bandung Conference (Box 83, Folder 635)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 69.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism - Soviet Model of Colonial-Imperialism (Box 83, Folder 636)
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism - Bandung Conference (Box 84, Folder 637)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 70.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism (Box 84, Folder 638)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 75.
  - Africa (Box 84, Folder 639)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 71.
  - Antarctica (Box 84, Folder 640)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 72.
  - Caribbean - Puerto Rico (Box 84, Folder 641)
  - Europe - General (Box 84, Folder 642)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 73.
  - Italy (Box 84, Folder 643)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 74.
  - Germany (Box 85, Folder 644)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 76.
  - Iceland and Finland (Box 85, Folder 645)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 77.
  - Arab-Israel (Box 85, Folder 646)
  - Arab-Israel (Box 85, Folder 647)
  - Near and Middle East - Policy Papers (Box 85, Folder 648)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 78.
  - India - General (Box 85, Folder 649)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 81.
  - India - Economic Aid and General (Box 85, Folder 650)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 80.
  - India - Tata Iron and Steel Company (Box 85, Folder 651)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 79.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Policy Papers (India, Philippines, Indonesia, Singapore) (Box 86, Folder 652)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 82.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Policy Papers (Indochina) (Box 86, Folder 653)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 83.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Overseas Chinese (Asian University) (Box 86, Folder 654)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 84.
  - South and Southeast Asia - General (Box 86, Folder 655)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 85.
  - South and Southeast Asia - General (Box 86, Folder 656)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 86.
  - Far East - China, Red China, Korea, and Formosa (Box 86, Folder 657)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 87.
  - Far East - Regional Data Book (Box 86, Folder 658)
  - Far East - Japan (Box 87, Folder 659)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 88.
  - Latin America - Policy Papers (Box 87, Folder 660)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 89.
  - Latin America - Policy Papers (Box 87, Folder 661)
  - Latin America - Regional Data Book (Box 87, Folder 662)
  - Latin America - Countries (General) (Box 88, Folder 663)
  - Latin America - Countries (Brazil) (Box 88, Folder 664)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 90.
  - Latin America - Countries (Chile and Guatemala) (Box 88, Folder 665)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 3, Folder 91.
  - Soviet Union - Exchange of Visitors (General) (Box 88, Folder 666)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 94.
  - Soviet Union - Policy Papers (Box 88, Folder 667)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 92.
  - Soviet Union - Soviet Orbit Propaganda (Box 88, Folder 668)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 93.
  - Soviet Union - Exchange of Visitors (Farmers) (Box 89, Folder 669)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 95.
  - Soviet Union - Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 670)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 96.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, January 1955 (Box 89, Folder 671)
  - Chronological Files - Classified, February 1955 (Box 89, Folder 672)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 97.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, March 1955 (Box 89, Folder 673)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 98.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, April 1955 (Box 89, Folder 674)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 99.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, May 1955 (Box 89, Folder 675)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 100.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, June 1955 (Box 89, Folder 676)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 101.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, July 1955 (Box 89, Folder 677)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 102.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, August 1955 (Box 89, Folder 678)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 103.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, September 1955 (Box 89, Folder 679)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 104.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, October 1955 (Box 90, Folder 680)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 105.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, November 1955 (Box 90, Folder 681)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 106.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, December 1955 (Box 90, Folder 682)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 107.
  - Chronological Files - Classified, January 1956 (Box 90, Folder 683)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, January 1955 (Box 90, Folder 684)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, February 1955 (Box 90, Folder 685)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, March 1955 (Box 90, Folder 686)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, April 1955 (Box 90, Folder 687)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, May 1955 (Box 91, Folder 688)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, June 1955 (Box 91, Folder 689)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, July 1955 (Box 91, Folder 690)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, August 1955 (Box 91, Folder 691)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, September 1955 (Box 91, Folder 692)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, October 1955 (Box 91, Folder 693)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, November 1955 (Box 92, Folder 694)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, December 1955 (Box 92, Folder 695)
  - Chronological Files - Unclassified, January 1956 (Box 92, Folder 696)
  - Congratulatory Letters (A-G) (Box 92, Folder 697)
  - Congratulatory Letters (H-M) (Box 92, Folder 698)
  - Congratulatory Letters (N-Z) (Box 93, Folder 699)
  - Resignation - NAR Letters (Box 93, Folder 700)
  - NAR Resignation (Box 93, Folder 701)
  - Congratulatory Letters Upon Resignation (Box 93, Folder 702)
  - Index to Files (Box 93, Folder 703)
  - Personal Chronological Files, June-September 1953 (Box 94, Folder 704)
  - Personal Chronological Files, October-December 1953 (Box 94, Folder 705)
  - Personal Chronological Files, January-March 1954 (Box 94, Folder 706)
  - Personal Chronological Files, April-June 1954 (Box 94, Folder 707)
  - Personal Chronological Files, July-September 1954 (Box 94, Folder 708)
  - Personal Chronological Files, October-December 1954 (Box 94, Folder 709)
  - Personal Chronological Files, January-March 1955 (Box 94, Folder 710)
  - Personal Chronological Files, April-June 1955 (Box 95, Folder 711)
  - Personal Chronological Files, July-September 1955 (Box 95, Folder 712)
  - Personal Chronological Files, October-December 1955 (Box 95, Folder 713)
  - Personal Chronological Files, January 1956 (Box 95, Folder 714)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - NAR Activities, post-December 31, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 715)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Clippings (Box 96, Folder 716)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - George S. Pettee (Box 96, Folder 717)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses (Box 96, Folder 718)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 96, Folder 719)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Foreign Policy Research Institute (Box 96, Folder 720)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Government Affairs Foundation (Box 96, Folder 721)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) (Box 96, Folder 722)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Letters to President (Box 96, Folder 723)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Non-Military Psychological Warfare (Box 96, Folder 724)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 110.
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Clippings - Foreign Policy (Box 96, Folder 725)
    April 1941 "Fortune" removed to Box 202.
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Overall Report - Action Program for Free World (Box 96, Folder 726)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Public Opinion Reports (Box 96, Folder 727)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico Panels (Box 96, Folder 728)
    See also Subseries 9, Box 4, Folder 112.
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 96, Folder 729)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - "What Is to Be Done?" (Box 97, Folder 730)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - "Can America Win the Cold War?" - Frank R. Barnett (Box 97, Folder 731)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Citizen's Commission on U.S. Foreign Policy - Dr. Sockman (Box 97, Folder 732)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Committee for International Freedom, Inc. - Karl Harr, Jr. (Box 97, Folder 733)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Council for a Bipartisan Foreign Policy - Bayless Manning (Box 97, Folder 734)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Major Policies of Republican Party - Franklin A. Lindsay (Box 97, Folder 735)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Research on National Security Problems - Franklin A. Lindsay (Box 97, Folder 736)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - "What Is to Be Done?" - William Kintner (Box 97, Folder 737)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Frank Barnett (Box 97, Folder 738)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Walt Rostow (Box 97, Folder 739)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - American Roundtable of Freedom - William Y. Elliott (Box 97, Folder 740)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Agenda (NAR's Notes) (Box 97, Folder 741)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-A Report (Box 97, Folder 742)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-B Report (Box 97, Folder 743)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-C Report (Box 97, Folder 744)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-D Report (Box 97, Folder 745)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-E Report (Box 97, Folder 746)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section I-F Report (General Comments at End of Session: Livermore) (Box 97, Folder 747)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section II-A Report (Box 97, Folder 748)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section II-B Report (Box 97, Folder 749)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section III Report (Box 97, Folder 750)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III An American Policy for the Next Decade - Millikan and Rostow (Box 97, Folder 751)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III An American Policy for the Next Decade - Comments, Summaries (Box 97, Folder 752)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Individual Papers - Kintner, Pettee, Linebarger (Box 97, Folder 753)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section IV-A Report (Box 97, Folder 754)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Section IV-B Report (Box 97, Folder 755)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Quantico III Attendance (Box 97, Folder 756)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Press Clips - before February 1956 (Box 97, Folder 757)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Press Clips - February (Box 97, Folder 758)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Press Clips - March (Box 97, Folder 759)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Press Clips - April (Box 97, Folder 760)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Chronologies - February, March (Box 97, Folder 761)
  - Nancy Hanks Files - Talent File (Box 97, Folder 762)
    Autographed oversized "elephant" removed to Box 202.
  - "Fortune Magazine", April 1941 (Box 202A, Folder 1789)